directorym.com 2004-07-10

# DirectoryM - Privacy Policy

Advertisers

Partners

Buyers

Corporate Info

Privacy Policy

  * DirectoryM has a strong commitment to respecting the privacy of all visitors to our directories. This policy covers how DirectoryM treats personal information that it collects and receives, including information related to your past use of DirectoryM products and services. "Personal information" is information about you that is personally identifiable such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 
  * This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that DirectoryM does not own or control, or to people that DirectoryM does not employ or manage. In particular, DirectoryM has no control over the privacy policies of any vendor website linked through our directories. 
  * DirectoryM collects personal information when you register your company with DirectoryM and when you submit an inquiry via DirectoryM directory pages. DirectoryM may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 
  * When vendors register their company we ask for information such as their name, phone number, email address, zip code, occupation, industry and various industry-based criteria. This information may be made available to the public as a listing in our directory pages. Additionally, this information may be made available to a user to whom you send a reply to an inquiry.
  * When you submit an inquiry we ask for information such as your name, email address, phone number and criteria specific to your inquiry. This information will only be released to those vendors that are selected on the directory page on which you submit an inquiry.
  * DirectoryM automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, DirectoryM cookie information, and the page you request. 
  * In accordance with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act, DirectoryM does not intend to record information submitted by children younger than 13 years old. Children under 13 years old should submit personally identifiable information to DirectoryM only with the explicit permission of their parent or legal guardian. 
  * DirectoryM will not contact children under age 13 about special offers or for marketing purposes. 
  * DirectoryM does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 
    * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with DirectoryM under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help DirectoryM communicate with you about offers from DirectoryM and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
    * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; 
    * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of DirectoryM's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 
    * We transfer information about you if DirectoryM is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, DirectoryM will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 
  * DirectoryM may set and access DirectoryM cookies on your computer. 
  * DirectoryM may update this policy. We will place a prominent notice on our site about significant changes in the way we treat personal information. 

Valid [XHTML](http://validator.w3.org/check/referer "Validate this document’s XHTML structure")    v2.0.254.29093 beta 7/10/2004 2:35:30 AM
